( tape recorder sounds )
( TV Din )
( Kaylee ) Ya ?
( tape player whirs with no sound )
Dad ?
( tape plays succesfully ) ( tape version of " Babar " )
( silence )
( small footsteps )
( Kevin ) One .
Two .
Three
( falling down stairs )
( child sobbing down the hall )
( adults footsteps )
( child sobs louder )
( car leaves driveway )
( silence )
( muffled cartoon music plays )
( music ends abruptly )
( door opens ) ( families footsteps enter )
( dads quiet footsteps )
( whisper ) Kaylee ?
( footsteps continue )
( dial tone )
( dialing )
( ringing )
( Dad ) So ... he 's fine
( Dad ) But Kevin , fell down the stairs
( Dad ) and hit his head
( Dad ) Mhmm ..
( Dad ) No . They didn 't even need to do stiches
( toilet flushes )
( Kaylee ) Dad ?
( silence )
( Kaylee ) Kevin .
( bed sheets rustle )
( eerie tone )
( blinds being pulled )
( Kaylee ) Dad ?
( kids footsteps on stairs )
( eerie tone )
( Kaylee ) Dad ?
( blinds being pulled )
( eerie tone )
( Kaylee ) Dad ?
( clumsy dialing )
( disconnected tone )
( dialing )
( abruptly hangs up )
( Videotape machine whirs )
( Kevin ) I cant sleep with the lights on .
( cartoons play quietly )
( Kaylee ) Kevin ?
( Kevin ) Ya ?
( Kaylee whispers ) Love you .
( Kevin ) Love you too .
( Kaylee ) Kevin .
( Kaylee ) I think it 's time to get up .
( cereal box rattles )
( Kaylee ) I 'm gonna go upstairs to get some stuff .
( Kaylees footsteps )
( rumaging through toy bin )
( footsteps stop abruptly )
( Kaylee ) Dad ?
( silence )
( footsteps fade )
( click )
( crayons on paper )
( drawing ceases )
( light switch is flicked on and off )
( drawing resumes )
( gentle snoring )
( movement on couch )
( little footsteps )
( Kaylee Whispers )
( Kevin ) How come no ones come yet ?
( Kaylee ) I don 't know .
( Kaylee ) Maybe we should just ..
( rapid thumping from upstairs )
( Kevin ) What was that ?
( Loud scrape )
( Kaylee whispers ) We should be quiet .
( cartoons play quietly )
( Kevin whispers )
( Kaylee whispers )
( Kevin )
( Kaylee )
( snoring )
( Kevins footsteps )
( Kevin ) Kaylee .
( rustling on couch )
( Kevin ) You have to come see this .
( two sets of footsteps )
( footsteps stop )
( eerie tone )
( Kevin ) Where did it go ?
( Kaylee ) Just hurry ...
( bathroom door closes )
( Kaylees slow footsteps )
( Kaylee gasps )
( Scream )
( Kaylee out of breath )
( Kevin ) Sorry .
( Kaylee ) What ? !
( Kevin )
( Kevin ) Gross !
( Kaylee ) Did you see anything ..
( Kaylee ) weird up ... stairs ?
( Kevin ) Like what ?
( rumaging through toys )
( Triumphant cartoon music )
( clicking of plastic blocks )
( cartoon volume quiet )
( snoring )
( strange voice ) Kaylee .
( strange voice )
( cartoon music fades to nothing )
( Kaylee ) Dad ?
( Dad whispers )
( Kaylee whispers ) I can 't see anything .
( Kaylee gasps )
( Mom ) Kaylee ?
Your ..
Your father and me
( door slams )
Kaylee .
( mom whispers )
( creaking )
( quiet struggle )
( stange voice whispers )
( Mom ) Someones here .
( creak )
( Mom moans )
( stange voice whispers )
( Mom ) Kaylee .
( Mom )
( bone crack )
( moaning quietly )
( inhuman squeal )
( Tone )
( Kevin )
( Kaylee ) Help me move the couch , okay ?
( clicking light switch )
( rustling through kitchen cabinets )
( Kevin )
( cartoons play quietly )
( TV muted )
( Kaylee breaths heavily )
( strange voice )
( silence )
( Kevin ) Kaylee ?
( Kevin ) Hello ?
( Kevins little footsteps )
( VCR winds up )
( Cartoon sounds resume )
( Kaylee breaths heavily )
( cartoons play loudly )
( Kevin clicks flashlight )
( urinating )
( cartoons play quiet ) ( Kevin snores )
( toys click and rustle )
( Triumphant cartoon music )
( Strange voice ) Kevin .
( Strange voice whispers ) Come to the basement .
( cartoon music fades away )
( silence )
( Kaylee muffled )
( deafening tone )
( cartoons play quietly )
( running steps come closer )
( running stops )
( Kevin out of breath )
( TV din from downstairs )
( rumaging through cabinets )
( strange voice )
( Kevin ) Hello ?
( strange voice ) Kevin .
( strange voice )
( body falls )
( cartoons play loudly )
( cartoons stop )
( cartoons play loudly ) ♪ ♪ Presto-Change-O ♪ ♪
( silence )
( cartoons play normally )
( Kevin rustles on carpet )
( clicking of plastic toys )
( Strange voice )
( Kevin stops playing )
( playing resumes )
( Strange voice ) Kevin .
( playing stops )
( Strange voice ) I want to ... play !
( playing resumes )
( drawer slams open )
( playing stops )
♪ ♪ Presto-Change-O ♪ ♪
( music stops )
( Kevin breaths heavily )
( Strange voice ) Kevin .
♪ ♪ Presto-Change-O ♪ ♪ ( rummaging cutlery )
( Kevin whimpers )
( saftey knife cranks )
( Strange voice )
( pained moaning from downstairs )
( sobbing and screaming )
( Strange voice ) Wake up .
( Kevins pained breathing )
( slow / clumsy footsteps )
( blankets rustle )
( cartoon music resumes )
( cartoon music distorts )
( audio stops ) ( Kevin breaths heavily )
( silence )
( ominous tone )
( slow footsteps through toys )
( unidentified beeping )
( clumsy bumping )
( flashlight click )
( off-hook tone )
( dial beep )
( dialing )
( ringing )
( operator heard faintly )
( Kevin whispers ) I hurt ...
( Kevin whispers ) .. myself and I feel sick .
( Kevin whispers ) Ya .
( Kevin whispers ) No .
( Kevin whispers ) Umm ... I
( Kevins continues faintly )
( Kevin whispers ) Ya .
( Kevin ) Ya .
( Kevin whispers ) No .
( Kevin whispers ) I 'm downstairs but the doors is gone .
( thud )
( blankets rustle )
( flashlight click )
( Kevin ) You did that .
( strange voice laughs uncannily )
( silence )
( Strange Voice ) Kevin .
( Kevin breaths shakily )
( sound static slowly grows )
( silence )
( Kevin ) How did you do that ?
( strange voice whispers )
( flashlight click )
( Kevin whimpers )
( Strange Voice ) It 's okay .
( Strange Voice ) I will pro-tect you .
( unidentified banging )
( Kevin breathes shakily )
( Strange Voice ) Keep going .
( Kevins breathing echos )
( Kevin ) Can I go back now ?
( faint echos in distance )
( Kevin whimpers )
( uncanny animal call echos )
( monster growls in distance )
( growls grow louder )
( quiet )
( flashlight click )
( cartoon music fades in )
( Cartoon boy sings ) ♪ ♪ I don 't have to worry ♪ ♪
♪ ♪ I don 't have to care ♪ ♪
( Cartoon boy sings ) ♪ ♪ My coat is very furry ♪ ♪
♪ ♪ I 'm a furry grizzly bear ♪ ♪
( cartoon melody continues )
( cartoon music grows chaotic )
♪ ♪
( innocent melody plays )
( silence )
( uncanny gasp )
( crawling echos )
( inhuman cries )
( VCR winds up )
( machine quietly whirs )
( machine loudly whirs )
( silence )
( eerie melody echos )
( music ceases )
( crawling echos )
( flashlight click )
( Loud Ring )
( silence )
( child whispers unclear )
( whisper grows deeper )
( audio dead )
( tape player whirs with no sound )
( clicks off )
( clicks )
( child cries )
( uncanny murmer )
( child screams )
( monster screams chaotically )
♪ ♪ Presto-Change-O ♪ ♪
( older child cries )
( uncanny murmer )
( older child screams )
( monster screams chaotically )
( Tone )
( monster growls chaotically )
♪ ♪ Presto-Change-O ♪ ♪
( Strange Voice laughs )
( tortured scream )
( monster screams chaotically )
♪ ♪ Presto-Change-O ♪ ♪
( Strange voice cackles )
( silence )
( flashlight click )
( Kevin ) Kaylee .
( Kevin )
♪ ♪ Heavenly melody ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
( Music slowly fades )
( Strange Voice )
( child )